Conservationists go to war over whether humans are the measure of nature’s value.
自然保护主义者为“人类是否为衡量自然价值的尺度”这一问题争得不可开交。
New Conservationists argue such trade-offs are necessary in this human-dominated epoch.
新自然保护主义者认为，在这个由人类主导的时代，这样的权衡取舍是必要的。
And they support “re-wilding”, a concept originally proposed by Soule where people curtail economic growth and withdraw from landscapes, which then return to nature.
他们还支持“再野化”——这一概念最初由苏莱提出，指人们抑制经济增长，从一些地域撤出，让这些地域随后回归自然。
New Conservationists believe the withdrawal could happen together with economic growth.
新自然保护主义者认为，这种撤出可以与经济增长同时发生。
The California-based Breakthrough Institute believes in a future where most people live in cities and rely less on natural resources for economic growth.
总部位于加利福尼亚州的突破研究所相信这样一种未来：大多数人住在城市里，在实现经济增长时更少依赖自然资源。
They would get food from industrial agriculture, including genetically modified foods, desalination, intensified meat production and aquaculture, all of which have a smaller land footprint.
他们将从工业化农业获取食物，包括转基因食品、海水淡化、集约化肉类生产和水产养殖，所有这些占用的土地都更少。
And they would get their energy from renewables and natural gas.
他们还将从可再生能源和天然气中获取能源。
Driving these profound shifts would be greater efficiency of production, where more products could be manufactured from fewer inputs.
推动这些深刻转变的将是更高的生产效率，即能用更少的投入制造出更多的产品。
And some unsustainable commodities would be replaced in the market by other, greener ones—natural gas for coal, for instance, explained Michael Shellenberger, president of the Breakthrough Institute.
突破研究所所长迈克尔·谢伦伯格解释说，一些不可持续的商品会在市场上被其他更环保的商品取代——比如用天然气取代煤炭。
Nature would, in essence, be decoupled from the economy.
从本质上说，自然将与经济脱钩。
And then he added a caveat: “We are not suggesting decoupling as the paradigm to save the world, or that it solves all the problems or eliminates all the trade-offs.”
接着，他又补充了一句限定性的说明：“我们并不是主张把脱钩当作拯救世界的范式，也不是说它能解决所有问题或消除所有权衡取舍。”
Cynics may say all this sounds too utopian, but Breakthrough maintains the world is already on this path toward decoupling.
悲观者可能会说，这一切听起来太过理想化，但突破研究所坚称，世界已经走上了这条通往脱钩的道路。
Nowhere is this more evident than in the United States, according to Iddo Wernick, a research scholar at the Rockefeller University, who has examined the nation’s use of 100 main commodities.
据洛克菲勒大学的研究学者伊多·沃尼克说，这一点在美国体现得最为明显；他考察过美国对100种主要商品的使用情况。
Wernick and his colleagues looked carefully at data from the U.S. Geological Survey National Minerals Information Center, which keeps a record of commodities used from 1900 through the present day.
沃尼克和同事们仔细研究了美国地质调查局国家矿产信息中心的数据，该中心保存着从1900年至今各类商品的使用记录。
They found that the use of 36 commodities (sand, iron ore, cotton, etc.) in the U.S. economy had peaked.
他们发现，美国经济中36种商品（如沙子、铁矿石、棉花等）的使用量已经达到峰值。
Another 53 commodities (nitrogen, timber, beef, etc.) are being used more efficiently per dollar value of gross domestic product than in the pre-1970s era.
按每美元国内生产总值计算，另外53种商品（如氮、木材、牛肉等）现在的使用效率都比20世纪70年代以前更高。
Their use would peak soon, Wernick said.
沃尼克说，它们的使用量很快就会达到峰值。
Only 11 commodities (industrial diamond, indium, chicken, etc.) are increasing in use (Greenwire, Nov. 6), and most of these are employed by industries in small quantities to improve systems processes.
只有11种商品（如工业金刚石、铟、鸡肉等）的使用量在增长（据《Greenwire》11月6日报道），而且其中大多数是各行业为改进系统流程而少量使用的。
Chicken use is rising because people are eating less beef, a desirable development since poultry farming has a smaller environmental footprint.
鸡肉的使用量在上升，是因为人们吃的牛肉减少了；这是一个可喜的变化，因为家禽养殖的环境足迹更小。
The numbers show the United States has not intensified resource consumption since the 1970s even while increasing its GDP and population, said Jesse Ausubel of the Rockefeller University.
洛克菲勒大学的杰西·奥苏贝尔说，这些数据表明，自20世纪70年代以来，美国即便在国内生产总值和人口不断增长的同时，也没有加大资源消耗。
“It seems like the 20th-century expectation we had, we were always assuming the future entailed greater consumption of resources,” Ausubel said.
“看起来，我们在20世纪抱有的预期就是：总以为未来必然意味着更多的资源消耗，”奥苏贝尔说。
“But what we are seeing in the developed countries is, of course, peaks.”
“但我们在发达国家看到的，当然是资源消耗已经达到峰值。”